Guide to the Office of University Development records, 1947-ongoing UA.14.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2018.0058, 2
  - Planned philathropy, Fall 2007 (Box 31)
  - Planned philathropy (McAllister and Feagle), Spring 2006 (Box 31)
  - Gift planning/planned philanthropy (Box 31)
  - Planned philathropy, Fall 2006 (Box 31)
  - Ways to give flyer, 2008 (Box 31)
  - Scholarship and fellowship, 2009 (Box 31)
  - Scholarship and fellowship, 2008 (Box 31)
  - Scholarship dinner, 2008 (Box 31)
  - Scholarship Dinner, 2008 (Box 32)
  - Scholarship Dinner Program, 2008 (Box 32)
  - Scholarships Dinner Invitation, 2007 (Box 32)
  - Scholarship Dinner Package, 2007 (Box 32)
  - Bass Dinner Program, 2005 (Box 32)
  - Bass Program, 2004 (Box 32)
  - Bass Program, 2003 (Box 32)
  - Bass Program, 2002 (Box 32)
  - Bass Program, 1999-2001 (Box 32)
  - Pocket Folder Bass Society of Fellows (Box 32)
  - JB Duke Recognition Celebration, 2008 (Box 32)
  - Scholarship Dinner, 2006 (Box 32)
    CD-R with the October 20, 2006 event
  - Duke Reading Room DC, 2008 February 12 (Box 32)
    CD-R with copyight
  - Student Thank You Notes, 2008 (Box 32)
  - Campaign Planning Materials, 2008 (Box 32)
  - Fundraising, 1990s (Box 32)
  - Fuqua Giving, 2003 June (Box 32)
  - Major Donors, 2005 January 18 (Box 32)
    Donor information restricted.
  - Campaign Voice, 2001 January (Box 32)
  - Major Gifts to Duke, 2003 (Box 32)
  - Campaign for Duke 1, 1983-1991 (Box 33)
  - Campaign for Duke Publications including identity standards manual (Box 33)
  - Campaign for Duke Print Materials (Box 33)
  - External Campaign Report, 2003 (Box 33)
  - Campaign for Duke folders on different schools (Box 33)
  - Campaign for Duke folders on different schools (Box 33)
  - Internal Campaign Report (Box 33)
  - Reports, Notes from Meetings, Presentations, and Financial Projections (Box 33)
  - Loose Duke Campaign Publications (Box 33)
  - Duke Travel Brochure Samples, 2010 (Box 33)
  - Cleveland City Club, 2006 (Box 34)
  - DAA Annual Report, 2008-2009 (Box 34)
  - DAA Homecoming, 2010 (Box 34)
  - DAA Identity Style Guide (Box 34)
  - DAA Samples, 2008 (Box 34)
  - Development Annual Report, 2005 (Box 34)
  - Development Annual Report, 2006 (Box 34)
  - Development Annual Report, 2007 (Box 34)
  - Development Annual Report, 2008 (Box 34)
  - Development Annual Report, 2009 (Box 34)
  - Divinity Dinner, 2010 (Box 34)
  - Economics Brochure (Box 34)
  - Duke Engage (Box 34)
  - Duke Gardens Case Statement, 2006 (Box 34)
  - Family Philanthropy, 2010 (Box 34)
  - GP End of Year Card, 2008-2010 (Box 34)
  - GP Campaign Report (Box 34)
  - Graduate School (Box 34)
  - JB Duke Event, 2006-2007 (Box 34)
  - JB Duke Event, 2009 (Box 34)
  - James B Duke Braxton Craven, 2011 (Box 34)
  - Jewish Life Brochure (Box 34)
  - Lemur Center (Box 34)
  - Making a Difference Strategic Plan (Box 34)
  - Nasher Booklet (Box 34)
  - Planned Philanthropy, Fall 2009 (Box 34)
  - Planned Philanthropy, Spring 2009 (Box 34)
  - Planned Philanthropy, Spring 2010 (Box 34)
  - Trinity Scholars, 2010 (Box 34)
  - SNF Dinner, 2006 (Box 34)
  - James B Duke Society and Founders Society, 2010 (Box 34)
  - Scholarship and Fellowships, 2009 (Box 34)
    includes audio and video on CD
  - Scholarships and Fellowships Dinner, 2010 (Box 34)
  - Scholarship and Fellowships, 2011 (Box 34)
  - Undergrad Admissions: Community (Box 34)
  - Undergrad Admiissions: Adventure (Box 34)
  - Undergrad Admissions: Frontier (Box 34)
  - Unlabeled Folder Duke Annual Fund (Box 35)
  - Duke Reunions 2010 Publications (Box 35)
  - Duke Reunions 2011 Publications (Box 35)
  - FAI (Financial Aid Initiative) Samples (Box 35)
  - Annual Fund Leadership Invitation, 2010 (Box 35)
  - Annual Fund Cabinet Invitation, 2009 (Box 35)
  - Annual Fund Honor Roll, 2008 (Box 35)
  - Annual Fund Honor Roll, 2007 (Box 35)
  - Annual Fund Holiday and Bday Cards, 2010 (Box 35)
  - Annual Fund Duke Story (Box 35)
  - Annual Fund Senior Stories, 2007 (Box 35)
  - Annual Fund Senior Stories, 2008 (Box 35)
  - Fall Ad Series, 2006 (Box 35)
  - FAI Student Speaker Competitions (Box 35)
  - Annual Fund Collateral, 2010 (Box 35)
  - Regional Campaign Council Handbook (Box 35)
  - Loose Printed Materials (Box 35)
  - DVDs for Scholarship Dinners and FAI movies (Box 35)
  - Campaign for Duke Sanford Institute (Box 35)
  - Duke Closing Campaign Packet (Box 35)
  - Campaign Media (Box 35)
  - Duke Campaign, 1980s-1990s (Box 36)
  - Annual Fund Development Materials (Box 36)
    includes slides
  - Case Statement Duke Fodder (Box 36)
  - Campaign Advertising Broadway at Duke (Box 36)
  - End Campaign-Impact (Box 36)
  - Greenspan/LH (Box 36)
    Video
  - Film Committee (Box 36)
  - Final Four (Box 36)
  - Slideshow (Box 36)
  - Volunteer Video/Powerpoint (Box 36)
  - Video 229 through 32, 2000 (Box 36)
  - Video 11-19-99, 1999 November 19 (Box 36)
  - Film: November 1-3, 2000 (Box 36)
  - Film: 11/15-16 (Box 36)
  - Edwards/17/00 (Box 36)
    video
  - Video Filming 4/11-4/15 (Box 36)
  - Retreat, 1997 May 02 (Box 36)
  - CPPS (Box 36)
  - Campaign Photography (Box 36)
  - Kickoff Invitation (Box 36)
  - Campaign Video (Box 36)
  - Kickoff (Box 36)
  - Graphics for Each School, 1998 (Box 36)
  - Graphics Identity Slides (Box 36)
  - Campaign Mark Artwork (Box 36)
  - Campaign Kickoff (Box 36)
  - Frequent Contact (Box 36)
  - News Not Release (Box 32)
  - Campaign Press (Box 32)
  - Clinical Trial Money, after 2000 (Box 32)
  - Board of Trustees Resolutions (Box 32)
  - Campaign WWW (Box 37)
  - LH Estimates (Box 37)
  - Campaign Numbers (Box 37)
  - Campaign End (Box 37)
  - End of Campaign Folders, 3 folders (Box 37)
  - Campaign Celebration Materials (Box 37)
  - University Case Statement Post Pub (Box 37)
  - Nicholas Faculty Leadership Initiative (Box 37)
  - Focus on the Finish (Box 37)
  - Assorted Invitations and Publications (Box 37)
  - Law School (Box 37)
  - Nicholas School (Box 37)
  - Perkins Library (Box 37)
  - Divinity School/Duke Chapel (Box 37)
  - Pratt Engineering (Box 37)
  - Second Round Arts and Sciences, 2002 (Box 37)
  - Athletics Case Statement Preparation (Box 37)
  - Second Round Athletics Case Statement, 2002 (Box 37)
  - Art Museum (Box 37)
  - Arts and Science (Box 37)
  - 2 Billion Dollar Goal Brochure (Box 37)
  - Case Statement Opinions, 1997 (Box 37)
  - Campaign Communications (Box 37)
  - First Round Campaign Figures, 1998 June (Box 37)
  - End of Campaign, 2003 (Box 37)
  - 2nd Round Campaign Figures, 2000-2001; 3 folders (Box 38)
  - Final Report, 1996-2003; 6 folders (Box 38)
  - Preliminary Campaign Ideas, 1995-1996 (Box 38)
  - Regional Major Gifts Info/RCC Info (Box 38)
  - Webwork (Box 38)
  - University Case Statement Prep, 1998 September (Box 38)
  - UCS Graduate Page, 1998 (Box 38)
  - Case Statement Comments, 1996 (Box 38)
  - Original Case Statement Comments (Box 38)
  - Who? Case Comments (Box 38)
  - Administration Case Statement Responses (Box 38)
  - President Trustees Case statement Responses (Box 38)
  - Preliminary Case Statement (Box 38)
  - President's Holiday Cards (Box 38)
  - Duke University Philanthropic Communication Audit, 2009 (Box 38)
  - DVD: Women's College of Duke University, 2002 November 08 (Box 39)
    DVD
  - Duke Alumni Association Annual Report, 2008-2009 (Box 39)
  - The Duke Idea (Box 39)
  - Duke Alumni Association Identity Style Guide (Box 39)
  - Duke Annual Fund Calendar, 2008 (Box 39)
  - Giving to Duke Annual Reports, 2008-2011 (Box 39)
  - Building on Excellence Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 39)
  - DVD: Six Duke Art Students (Box 39)
  - Duke Forward: The Arts, 2012-2013 (Box 39)
  - Iron Dukes/Athletics Brochure, Duke Forward materials (13 items) (Box 39)
  - Duke Forward: Bass Connections (Box 39)
  - The Campaign for Duke VHS (Box 39)
    VHS
  - Duke Durham Neighborhood Partnership Brochure (Box 39)
  - Duke Gardens Brochures and Reports (7 items) (Box 39)
  - Duke Catholic Center (Box 39)
  - Duke Communications Report (Box 39)
  - Duke Chapel Brochure (Box 39)
  - Duke Forward Divinity School, 2013-2014 (Box 39)
  - Duke Divnity School (Box 39)
  - Duke Endowment Flyer and Manual (2 items) (Box 39)
  - Duke Forward Energy (Box 39)
  - Affording Opportunity (5 items, including DVD) (Box 39)
  - Duke Center for Financial Economics (Box 39)
  - Duke Forward Kickoff (3 items, including DVD) (Box 39)
  - Fuqua School of Business (9 items) (Box 39)
  - Genome (4 items) (Box 39)
  - Planned Philanthropy (7 items) (Box 39)
  - Global Health Institute (9 items) (Box 39)
  - Duke Forward Graduate School and Brochure (Box 39)
  - BOT Directories, 2006-2008 (Box 39)
  - Chronicle: 30 years: The Silent Vigil, 1998 April 06 (Box 39)
  - Duke Forward: Innovation and Entrepeneurship (Box 39)
  - Kern Institute for Ethics (6 items) (Box 39)
  - Duke Forward School of Law and Brochure (Box 39)
  - Duke Lemur Center (5 items) (Box 39)
  - Duke Libraries (4 items) (Box 39)
  - Duke School of Medicine Magazine and Duke Forward Campaign Booklet (Box 39)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra Brochure and Flyer (Box 39)
  - Nasher Museum (6 items) (Box 39)
  - Nicholas School (5 items) (Box 39)
  - School of Nursing Duke Forward Booklet (Box 39)
  - School of Engineering (5 items) (Box 39)
  - Sanford School (5 items) (Box 39)
  - Angier B Duke Scholarship (2 items) (Box 39)
  - Social Science Research Institute Magazine (Box 39)
  - Duke Student Affairs (Box 39)
  - Duke TIP Pamphlets (Box 39)
  - Duke Clinical Research Unit (Box 39)
  - Duke Trinity (5 items) (Box 39)
  - Duke Forward Invites, Chicago, Miami, DC, and LA (Box 39)
  - J. B Duke Recogniton Celebration Program, 2013 November 16 (Box 39)
  - Invitations and Save the Date Cards (Box 39)
  - Duke Forward Campaign Report, 2013 (Box 39)
  - Partnership in the Arts (Box 39)
  - Buildings and Endowments, 2012 (Box 39)
  - Duke Forward (4 items) (Box 39)
  - Duke Athletics Brochures (Box 39)
  - Campaign for Duke DVD, 2004 (Box 39)
  - Designing Duke's Fundraising Campaign, 2011 (Box 39)
  - Oversize Duke Medicine Brochures (Box 39)
  - Buildings and Endowments, 2011-2017 (Box 39)
  - Haiti Booklet (Box 39)
  - School of Public Policy Toolkit and Reports (Box 39)
  - Duke Endowment and Building Report, 2010 (Box 39)
  - Assorted Duke Annual Reports and Brochures (Box 39)
  - Duke Engineering (Box 39)
  - Duke Oversize Brochure (Box 39)
  - Oversize Duke Medicine Brochures (Box 46)
  - Duke Medicine Materials (Box 40)
  - Oversize Hand-Drawn Duke University Poster (Oversize-folder 1)
- Accession UA2018.0060, 3
  - Honor Rolls, 1991-1998 (Box 47)
  - Historical Honor Roll, 1977-1984 (Box 47)
  - Honor Rolls and Reports, 1979-1983 (Box 47)
  - Historical Honor Roll, 1970-1979 (Box 47)
  - Honor Rolls, 1998-2003 (Box 47)
  - Historical Honor Roll, 1947-1967 (Box 47)
  - Honor Rolls, 2004 (Box 48)
  - Honor Rolls, 2006-2007 (Box 48)
  - Honor Rolls, 2007-2008 (Box 48)
  - Honor Rolls, 2004-2009 (Box 48)
    lots of loose brochures and pamphlets, many with same title but different list
  - 50th year reunion programs, 1988-2002 (Box 48)
  - Photos (Box 48)
    photographs
  - Honor Rolls, 1988-1989 (Box 48)
  - Honor Rolls, 1989-1990 (Box 48)
  - Honor Rolls, 1990-1991 (Box 48)
  - Duke Financial Aid Initative Final Report, 2000-2008 (Box 48)
  - Description of Second Annual Scholarships Banquet/Speech by Arthur Cassell, 1980 (Box 48)
  - Benchmark Newsletter, the Campaign for Duke, October 1999-September 2003 (Box 48)
- Accession UA2018.0067, 4
  - Final Internal Campaign report, June 14, 2018 (Box 41)
  - Annual Impact Reports, 2011-2015 (Box 41)
  - S.A.P. Campaign Blueprint docs, circa 2012 (Box 41)
  - Campaign Coding Design, circa 2012 (Box 41)
  - Sample Portfolio folder for D.F. Ambassadors, 2012-2014 (Box 41)
  - Folders with Case Statements and Launch event DVDs, 2012 (Box 41)
  - Sample Duke Forward Stationery and folders, 2012-2017 (Box 41)
  - Folders for all Duke Forward on the Road and other signature campaign events, with (most) all printed communication pieces - toolkits, invitations, save-the-dates, reminders, programs, table tents, etc., 2012-2017 (Box 42)
  - Campaign Planning Retreats and Committee meetings, Binders and folders, 2008-2013 (Box 43)
  - Some staff briefing packets for Duke Forward on the road events, 2008-2013 (Box 43)
  - Sample Give-Away items, 2011-2017 (Box 44)
  - School, unit, initiative, and program-centric Duke Forward brochures, 2011-2017 (Box 44)
  - Stationery items, 2011-2017 (Box 44)
  - Some working files on: beans' rollout, goal setting and goal projections, interdisciplinary initative, capital projects, 2009-2013 (Box 44)
  - Staff working files for mostly Regional Rollout, Duke Forward on the Road Events, 2012-2017 (Box 45)
  - Meeting agendas and notes, planning, outcomes, Campaign Steering Committee, Delegates Retreats I and II, Regional Rollout planning, volunteer management, Campaign Finale Celebration, final campaign reporting, 2012-2017 (Box 45)
  - Some large folio design proofs for Duke Forward Campaign Case Statement and Events, 2012-2017 (Box 46)
- Accession UA2018.0083
  - Mr. and Mrs. Stephen Harward (Coralynn) (Box 49)
    Restricted due to donor information; must be screened before use.
  - Harward Plaque Ceremony, October 15, 1994 (Box 49)
  - William Griffith (Box 49)
  - Fowlie, Wallace (Box 49)
  - Leonard Pardue (Box 49)
  - Herb Neubauer (Box 49)
  - Samuel D. Cook (Box 49)
  - Davis, Evelyn Y. (Box 49)
  - Pishko, Mary Jane (Box 49)
  - Historical Blurbs, 2 folders (Box 49)
    Contains photos
  - Arrangements, October 30, 2003 (Box 49)
  - Sample Invitation: Sheffield Dedication, March 4, 2000 (Box 49)
  - Sample Invitation: Franklin Center Dedication, 2001 February 9 (Box 49)
  - Sample Invitation: Freeman Dedication, October 24, 1999 (Box 49)
  - Peter Lange Signed Print, 2004 (Box 49)
  - A Duke Conversation: Making a Difference (Box 49)
    Contains CD/DVD
  - Assorted Development Event Invitations (Box 49)
  - Celebrating Duke (Box 49)
  - The Campaign for Duke: Regional Campaign Councils Handbook (Box 49)
  - Photos (Box 49)
- Accession UA2018.0091
  - Duke University Women's Initiative, 3 folders (Box 50)
  - Heritage Society desk calendars, 2016-2017 (Box Box 51)